# **Abdur Raziq Khan**

# Web Developer



abdurraziq226@gmail.com



+92 (346) 484 8226



1530218387071



October, 05, 1993



http://abdurraziq.ml

## Why Abdur?

Performance oriented and focused on Angular and Node.js to immaculate and grows the presence of a websites development. I have 3 years of hands-on experience coding websites and applications efficiently.

- Good experience in developing Single Page Applications using Angular with integrated API's.
- Goal driven professional with blend of academic credentials, analytical agility and relentless enthusiasm towards Web Development planning, an execution, capable of executing measures to maintain accuracy of the strategy to achieve the goals.

#### **CORE STRENGTHS & ENABLING SKILLS**

- HTML
- Bootstrap
- Zeplin
- Git

- Angular
- Node.jsGitLab
- Jira

- JavaScript, JQuery
- APIs Integration
- MySQL, MongoDB
- BitBucket

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Kiwi Services, Khayaban-e-Sir Syed, Rawalpindi, Pak

Worked as "Jr. Web Developer", Nov 2018 – April 2019

#### **Responsibilities/Accomplishments:**

- Work as an individual and as a part of a team. Fully follow all operating procedures, and was managing frontend and backend.
- Delivered excellent and net coding experiences in order to maximize efficiency in code.
- Implement a responsive design structure to ensure improved web and mobile user experience using Angular, bootstrap, HTML, CSS, and also manage to work on Node.js.
- Fixed performance issue with client side JavaScript. Used GitHub for source control.

#### Casa De Tech – Software house, F-11 Markaz, Islamabad, Pak

Worked as "Web Developer", Aug 2019 – Jan 2021

- Manage to code frontend of application through technologies like Angular, HTML, Bootstrap, CSS, JS and jQuery. In addition, focus on user experience and responsiveness of applications.
- Worked on projects like casadetech, studypooling, therubik, AMS, 24/7 games, metwah and etc.

#### LEAD for SDGs, Sector E-11/2 Islamabad, Pak

Worked as "IT Management Volunteer", July 2020 – Oct 2020

- Assisted in smooth programme implementation activities in the Islamabad office. Also, facilitated program
  team in managing Webinars, Zooms meetings, workshops, in Islamabad, Karachi and Quetta.
- Updated Programme's database with the contact details of key stackholders.

## O3 Interfaces (UBL Digital Partner), I-11, Islamabad, Pak

Works as "Frontend Developer", May 2021 - Present

- I am working on project "Fusion Inspect" frontend from scratch. Have worked on all the major modules. Fusion Inspect is a bug/crash reporting, app performance monitoring, in-app chats and user surveys for mobile apps.
- Currently, working on a UBL project "CLOS" using development tool Visualizer version 9.
- Manage to code frontend of application through technologies like Angular. Also, works on API's integration and code deployment to bitbucket as changes are made. Further, I am focused on better approach of constant improvement of look and feel of a product.

### PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATION

**International Islamic University** (Sep 2014 – May 2019)

BS in Computer Science

Address: I-9, Islamabad, Pakistan